Bigger, faster, hungrier.
Anacondas: Trail of Blood is a adventure, horror,
thriller film directed by Don E. FauntLeRoy.
A genetically created Anaconda, cut in half, regenerates itself into two
new aggressive giant snakes, due to the Blood Orchid.
Dr. Amanda Hayes, played by Crystal Allen.
Jackson, played by Linden Ashby.
Scott, played by Danny Midwinter.
Alex, played by Calin Stanciu.
Heather, played by Ana Ularu.
Armon, played by Claudiu Bleonţ.
Anacondas: Trail of Blood is a 2009 American horror
thriller television film directed by Don E.
FauntLeRoy and starring Crystal Allen, Linden Ashby,
Danny Midwinter, and John Rhys-Davies.
The film is a sequel to Anaconda 3: Offspring (2008) and the
fourth installment in the Anaconda film series.
It premiered on Sci Fi on February 28, 2009.
It was followed by Lake Placid vs.
Anaconda (2015), a crossover sequel with Lake Placid franchise.
The film explores themes of experiment, human vs nature, snake, predator, woods.
The tone is dark and intense.